[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はなし' read in word?",
        "answer": "Розмова, діалог"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'みせます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Показувати"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はじめます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Починати"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おしえます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Пояснювати, повідомляти"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'じゅう, しょ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Адреса"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Йти (опади)"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'なまえ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Ім*я"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'すぐ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Одразу"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しお' read in word?",
        "answer": "Сіль"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'さとう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Цукор"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'コピーします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Робити копію"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'また' read in word?",
        "answer": "Знову"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ゆっくり' read in word?",
        "answer": "Повільно"
    }
]
